Guide to the David Wolf Collection of American Musical Theater
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiocassettes
  - Musicals
    - The Girl Most Likely To..., Vocal Selections, Musical Theatre Works reading, 2000 August 22; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613675)
      "The Doctors' Masterpiece"
      "End of the Line (reprise)"
      "Hey There Beautiful"
      "Looks Can Kill (Murder Sequence)"
      "I'm Onto You"
      "Beautiful World"
    - The Girl Upstairs, undated; 2 (Box 15)
      - Stephen Sondheim sings and plays the score, undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613683)
        Bring on the Girls
        The Girls Upstairs
        Rain on the Roof
        Pleasant Little Kingdom
        Too Many Mornings
        Who's that Woman?
        One More Kiss
        That Old Piano Roll
        Boy, Can That Boy Foxtrot
        Could I Leave You?
      - Sung and played by Stephen Sondheim; Follies, undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613691)
    - The Graduate, Bob Merrill sings his score, undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613709)
    - Grind
      - Act II, 1985 March 1; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613717)
      - Act One, Baltimore; Act One concluded, Act Two beginning, 1985 March 1; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614269)
      - Original Broadway Cast Recording, 1 (Box 16)
      - Grind, Harold Prince organization, 1984 June; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614277)
        Wind-up Dolly
        Sweet Thing
        I Beat Up the Best
        Boys Will Be Boys
        Cadaua
        Will You Work?
        Katie My Love
        All Things to One Man
        George
        Grind
        Rabbity Stew
        Chocolate Dollies
        Good as New (No Cause for Compaint)
        Poor Little Fish
        I Never Put It in Writing
        I Talk, You Talk
        Timing
        Down
        A Century of Progress
        Grind (reprise)
      - Grind, 1984 October; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614285)
        There is a list of contents is included with this audiocassette.
        This Must Be the Place
        My Daddy Always Taught Me to Share
        Why, Mama, Why?
        Never Put It in Writing
        I Talk - You Talk
        His Love is Shining
        My Daddy Always Taught Me (reprise)
    - Grover's Corners, undated
      - Tom Jones and Harvey Schmidt, undated; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614293)
      - MTW Presentation (Nat Alliance), Jones/Schmidt, undated; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614301)
    - Gypsy
      - Act I, Ethel Merman (closing night), 1961 March 25; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614319)
        Cast includes: Jack Klugman, Julienne Marie, Merle Louise, Betty Bruce, Faith Dane, June Squibb, Jeffrey Bolton, Alice Playton, Jeanne Tanzy, and Susan Willis.
      - Act II, Ethel Merman, 1961 March 25; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614335)
      - Act One, start of Act Two, Live Imperial Theatre (closing performance), 1961 March 25; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614350)
      - Act Two, Live, closing show, 1961 March 25; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614343)
      - Act One and Two, "Momma's Talking Soft"/"Nice She Ain't", undated; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614327)
    - Gilbert Loves Anne of Green Gables, undated; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614368)
    - Harold and Maude: The Musical, 2002; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614376)
    - The Happiest Girl in the World, 1985
      - Part One, 1985 July 27-August 2; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614384)
      - Part Two, 1985 July 27-August 2; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614392)
    - He, undated; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614400)
    - Hooray! It's a Glorious Day...And All That!, undated
      - Tape One, undated; 1 (Box 16, Item barcode 39002104614418)
      - Tape Two, undated; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614616)
    - Hot Spot, undated; 2
      - Recorded Live, undated; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614624)
        Welcome to Our Country (Welcome Dance)
        This Little Yankee
        Wouldn't You Like to Know?
        A Little Trouble
        Nebraska
        Hey, Love
        Party
        Rich, Rich, Rich
        That's Good - That's Bad
        I Think the World of You
        Gabie
        Big Meeting Tonight
        Russian Dance
        It's a Far, Far Better Thing
        Don't Laugh - Finale
        Don't Laugh
        Don't Take My Word
        Show Me
      - Hot Spot, undated; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614632)
    - How To Succeed In Business Without Really Trying, undated; 1 (Box 17)
      This audiocassette is commercial. It has not been digitized.
    - Juno
      - Musical Theater Lab, Tape Two, 1992 August 27; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614640)
        You Poor Thing
        My True Heart
        Bird Upon the Tree
        Music in the House
        It's Not Irish
        The Liffey Waltz (reprise)
        Hymn
        Ireland's Eye
        You Poor Thing (reprise)
        Old Sayin's (reprise)
        For Love
        One Kind Word/I Wish It So (reprise)
        Where?
        Finale
      - Juno Composer Demo; Regina Demo, undated; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614657)
        Songs from "Juno" and "Regina"
        Daarlin' Man
        I Wish It So
        Song of the Ma
        Quarrel Song
        What is the Stars
        One Kind Word
        From This Out
        Ireland Eye
        You're the Girl
        You Poor Thing (Troubles)
        On a Day Like This
        Bird Upon a Tree
        Farewell Me Buddy
        Finale: One Kind Word, I Wish It So, Bird Upon the Tree
        What Will It Be
        Best Thing Of All
        Rain Quartette
        Lionette
    - Let 'Em Eat Cake, undated; 4
      - Act One, undated; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614665)
      - Act Two, undated; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614673)
      - Act One, undated; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614681)
        "Wintergreen for President"
        "Tweedledee for President"
        "Union Square"
        "Down with Everything That's Up"
        "Shirts by Millions"
        "Comes the Revolution"
        "Mine"
        "Climb Up the Social Ladder"
        Reprise: "Comes the Revolution"
        "On and On and On"
        Finale: "I've Brushed My Teeth", "Mothers of the Nation", "Let 'Em Eat Cake"
      - Act Two, undated; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614699)
        "Blue, Blue, Blue"
        "No Comprenez, No Capish, No Versteh!"
        "Why Speak of Money When There's Love?"
        "When Judges Doff the Ermine"
        "Up and At 'Em"
        "The Trial of Throttlebottom"
        "That's What He Did!"
        "I Know a Foul Ball"
        "Throttle Throttlebottom"
        "A Hell of a Hole"
        "It Isn't What You Did, It's What You Didn't"
        "First Lady and First Gent"
        "Hanging Throttlebottom in the Morning"
    - Light On My Feet, 4
      - Act One and Two, 1996 September 20; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614707)
      - Reading, Act One, 1996 September 20; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614715)
      - Reading, Act Two, 1996 September 20; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614723)
      - Songs only, master, 1996 September 20; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614731)
    - Little Me
      - Live, Act One (1982 Revival), 1982 February 3; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614749)
      - Act Two (1982 Revival), undated; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614756)
      - Live, Act II, 1982 February 3; 1 (Box 17, Item barcode 39002104614764)
      - Live I, undated; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616520)
    - A Little Night Music
      - Act Two, 1973 April 23; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616538)
      - Act One, 1973 April 23; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616546)
      - Act One, Boston, 1973 January 23; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616553)
      - Act Two, Boston, 1973 January 23; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616561)
      - Act One, Act Two, undated; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616579)
      - Act II, opening night of world premiere, Colonial Theatre, Boston, Mass., 1973 January 23; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616587)
      - Backer's Audition; Sweeney Todd - Backer's Audition Part 2, 1992 November; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616595)
        with Steve Sondheim and Hal Prince
      - Act I, opening night of world premiere, Colonial Theatre, Boston, Mass., 1973 January 23; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616603)
      - Live I, undated; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616611)
      - Live, part II, undated; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616629)
    - Lolita, My Love
      - Lolita, My Love, undated; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616637)
      - Songs Only, Acts 1 + 2, undated; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616645)
      - (Lerner, Barry) Original Cast, Act One, Act Two (beginning), undated; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616652)
    - Love Life
      - Demo Act II conclusion (Lerner/Weill), Demo Appendix, undated; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616660)
      - Demo Act I (Lerner/Weill), Act II, undated; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616678)
      - Act I and II, 1990 March 12; 1 (Box 18, Item barcode 39002104616686)
    - The Magic Hat, Unicorn Tales, 1977 December 5; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616363)
    - March of the Falsettos, 1981 April; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616371)
    - Maltese Unicorn, Unicorn Tales, Alex and the Wonderful Do-Wah Lamp, 1978 April 4; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616389)
    - Merrily We Roll Along
      - Merrily We Roll Along; Honey, 1981, undated; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616397)
      - Merrily I, 1981 November 15; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616405)
      - Merrily II, 1981 November 15; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616413)
      - Merrily Act I, 1981 October 26; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616421)
      - Merrily Act II, 1981 October 26; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616439)
      - Merrily We Roll Along, La Jolla - Act One, undated; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616447)
      - Merrily We Roll Along, La Jolla - Act Two, undated; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616454)
    - Miami, undated; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616462)
    - Minnie's Boys, 1970; 1 (Box 19)
    - A Mother's Kisses, undated; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616470)
      Look at Those Faces
      There Goes My Life
      Left by the Wayside
      He's Got Meg
      Every Body's a Dancer
      When You Gonna Learn (slow)
      Wait Baby Wait
      Fellas Kiss Their Dads
      When You Gonna Learn (fast)
      They Won't Regret It
      I Told Them We Were Lovers
      I Have a Terrible Secret
      Cromwell Music Inc.
    - My One and Only
      - My One and Only Act I, 1983 May 1; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616488)
      - My One and Only Act II, Preview 2, 1983 May 1; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616496)
    - The New Yorkers
      - The New Yorkers Act I, Stamford, 1993 March 13; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616504)
      - The New Yorkers Act II, Stamford, 1993 March 13; 1 (Box 19, Item barcode 39002104616512)
    - No For An Answer / Regina Act One, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616694)
    - Regina, Act Two and Three, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616702)
    - On Your Toes, Act One, 1983; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616728)
    - One Night Stand, 1980 October 25; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616710)
      Bows
      Everybody Loves Me
      Traveling
      Go Out Big
      Someday Soon
      For You
      Love Song
      Somebody Stole My Kazoo
      Long Way From Home
      Too Old
    - Oskar and Steve, Willard, Hammerstein Interview/Sondheim Interview, 1976 April 30; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616736)
      "Pacific Overtures" interview and "Conversation Piece" from "Side by Side", Australian cast, cut from London cast recording.
    - Rags, 1991; 2 (Box 20)
      These two audiocassettes are commercial. They have not been digitized.
    - Reuben, Reuben
      - Act One, Music and Lyrics: Marc Blitzstein, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616751)
      - Act Two, Music and Lyrics: Marc Blitzstein, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616769)
    - The Rink, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616744)
    - Roza, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616777)
      Side 1 / Side 2
      Happiness
      Is Me
      The Lion Will Dance with the Lamb
      Live a Little
      Life is Ahead of Me
      Merci
      House in Algiers
      Meet Me Halfway
      Don't Make Me Laugh
      Crazy People
    - Señor Discretion
      - Songs Only, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616793)
      - master, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616801)
    - Sunday in the Park with George, 1983 July 22; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616819)
    - Where's Charley?, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616827)
      Make a Miracle
      Once in Love with Amy
      Saunter Away
      The Bee
      Your Own College Band
    - Zorro, the Musical, demo, 1996; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616835)
      Opening
      The Adventure Begins
    - 70 Girls, 70; Golden Gate, demos, undated; 1; 00:31:21; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614004)
    - Untitled musical (Price/Walton), undated; 1; 00:20:00 (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614012)
      There is a list included with this audiocassette.
      Fly, Boy Fly
      Dreaming, Once Again
      Daisy Abbott
      Daisies for Daisy
      Meyer Weissberg
      She Sang My Song
      He Didn't Leave Me Flat
      Max's Death
      Hilda's Death (End It All)
      Let Her Remember Me
  - Composer/Singer
    - Abbott Tribute, Pt. 1, undated; 1; 02:02:49 (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614020)
    - Music by Marc Blitzstein; Reuben, Reuben, Regina, Juno, undated; 1; 01:26:36; Static, clicks and pops can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614038)
      There is a list of contents with this audiocassette.
      "The Cradle Will Rock": Nickel Under the Foot
      "The Cradle Will Rock": Hotel Lobby
      "No For an Answer": Penny Candy
      "No For an Answer": Francie
      "Regina": Lionnet
      "No For an Answer": Fraught
      "No For an Answer": Modest Maid
      "The Guests": Variation Two
      "The Guests": Pas de Deux
      "The Guests": Three-Four Dance
      "Reuben, Reuben": Musky and Whiskey
      "Reuben, Reuben": There Goes My Love
      "Reuben, Reuben": Sleep
      "Reuben, Reuben": San Gennaro
      "Regina": What Will It Be?
      "Regina": The Best Thing of All
      "Regina": Rain Quartet
      "Regina": Finale
      "Juno": commercial demo
      "Juno": My True Heart
      "Juno": I Wish It So
      "Juno": One Kind World
    - Barbara Cook Live at the Cafe Carlyle, 1991 October-1992 October 22; 1; 01:34:41; The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard in the last 47 minutes of the program. The program ends abruptly. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614046)
    - Noel Coward Sings Noel Coward, 1988; 1 (Box 21)
    - Sheldon Harnick, Part I, undated; 1; 01:03:31; Static can be heard on the tape. The program ends abruptly. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614053)
    - John Kander and Fred Ebb sing "The Skin of Our Teeth", 1994 November 4; 1; 01:05:47 (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614061)
    - John Kander and Fred Ebb sing "Flora, The Red Menace", 1987; 1; 00:59:08; Static can be heard on the tape. A warble is heard druing the program. The program is distorted at times. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614079)
      Graduation Song
      The Kid Herself
      All I Need is One Good [Break]
      It's Not Every [Day of the Week]
      Sign Here
      A Quiet Thing
      The Flame
      Five Flights Up
      Hello, Waves
      I Got a Right to Know
      You Ain't Seen Nothin' Yet
      Express Yourself
      Keepin' It Hot
      Sing Happy
      You are You
      I Can Go On
    - Kleban's Hot 100, undated; 1; 01:35:16; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. High background noise can also be heard. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614087)
      Light on My Feet
      Harold
      Paris Through the Window
      One More Beautiful Song
      The Artist's Mother
      Friday at Four
      Charm Song
      Henry Potter (Barbara Mosher)
      Follow Your Star
      Mona
      Making Up Ways
      Do It Yourself
      Food Songs
      Bacchus
      Reviews
      Fountain in the Garden
      Four O'Clock
      Love Me, Love My Tap Dance
      The Strawberry Girl
      I Choose You
      Birdies Sing
      The Chippermonkie Song
      Self-Portrait: Early
      I Love Your You
      Diana
      Under Separate Cover
      Next Best Thing
      Henry
      Gauguin's Shoes
      Better
      Say Something Funny
      When the Dawn Breaks
      Self-Portrait: Final
      David
    - Kleban Songs, undated; 1; 01:33:35; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614095)
    - Alan Jay Lerner at the Y, 1971; 1; 01:22:52; Clicks and pops can be heard on the tape. Static is also heard. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614103)
      How to Handle a Woman
      A Hymn to Him
      I Talk to the Trees
      Wouldn't It Be Loverly?
      Come to the Ball
      On the Street Where You Live (JT cromwell)
      Come Back to Me
      I'm Glad I'm Not Young Anymore
      I Loved You Once in Silence (Baird)
      Gigi
      Camelot-Gear Day-Accustomed
    - Lerner sings "The Little Prince" and "Lolita" and Gerard Kenny sings "My Man Godfrey", undated; 1; 01:02:59; Static, clicks and pops can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614111)
      It's a Hat
      Matters of Consequence
      I'm On Your Side
      Garbage Isn't What It Used to Be
      I'm Dancing My Blues Away
      Some People
      Hillary Bacon of Beacon Hill
      Happy Thanksgiving
      It Was you Again / I've Been Married
      The Same Old Song
      The Broken Promise Land of 15
      I Must Have her
      Ramsdale, VT
      I'll Buy you Bubblegum
      How Far is It to the Next T
    - Stephen Sondheim at Lyrics and Lyricists, 1971 May 2; 1; 02:03:56; The program ends abruptly. The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614129)
      The Reason Why (lyric)
      Love is in the Air
      Invocation
      Trouble (lyric by Shevelove)
      So Many People
      Getting Married Today
      Bring on the Beautiful Girls
      The Echo Song
      Parade in Town
      Amy's Song (The Wedding is Off)
      Can That Boy Foxtrot
      I Remember
      Marry Me a Little
      Multitudes of Amys
      Happily Ever After
    - Billy Jay Stein, 2 Songs, undated; 1; 01:24:29; Static, clicks and pops can be heard on the tape. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614137)
      Contents include "The Last Walt" and "Breakfast in Bed".
    - 1958-1959 TV Themes and Songs (Lonny), undated; 1; 00:45:03; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614145)
      I'm Sorry
      3 Stooges
      Rawhide
      Peter Gunn
      Have Gun Will Travel
      Only Sixteen
      Purple People Eater
      Sea Hunt
      Wagon Train
      Rocky + Bullwinkle
      Cracking Up
      Huckleberry Hound
      Hawaiian Eye
      Maverick
      Welcome to the Club
      Gleason Show
      Perry Mason
      Oh Yea
      Donna Reed
      Leave It to Beaver
      Dobie Gillis
      I Love Lucy
      Wonderful World
      It's Not For Me to Say
      Because of You
    - Leonard Bernstein Revisited; symphonic dances from West Side Story, orchestral suite from On the Waterfront and prelude, fugue and riffs, undated; 1; 01:30:26; Static, clicks and pops can be heard on the tape. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002104614152)
      Conquering the City (Wonderful Town)
      Lonely Me (Wonderful Town)
      Big Stuff (Fancy Free)
      We are Women (Candide-London)
      Bright + Black (1600 Pennsylvania Avenue)
      Another Love/Deam with Me (Peter Pan)
      Rio Bamba
      The President Jefferson March (1600 Pennsylvania Avenue)
      It's Got to Be Bad to Be Good
      The Story of My Life (Wonderful Town)
      Take Care of This House (1600 Pennsylvania Avenue)
      Ain't Got No Tears Left
      Ringaroundtherosie (Candide)
      Symphonic Dances from "West Side Story"
      Symphonic Suite from "On the Waterfront"
      Prelude, Fugue, and Riffs
  - Interviews, etc.
    - Panel #10, "Abbott Interviewed," Closing Remarks: Garson Kanin; Panel #8 Cont'd "Comedy", Panel #9 "B'way in the 1950's", undated; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616850)
    - Closing Remarks continued, Panel #4, "Oliver Smith", undated; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616843)
    - Opening Remarks: Prince, Panel #1 "Broadway in the 1930s", undated; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616868)
    - Richard Rodgers Interview + Bix, 1990 March 10; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616876)
    - Comden and Greene Symposium, 2001 November 25; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616884)
    - A Party with B. Comden and A. Green, "Live" in Florida, 1991; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616892)
      A list of musical selections is included with this audiocassette.
      I Said Good Morning
      The Reader's Digest
      Baroness Bazooka
      New York, New York
      Lonely Town
      Lucky to be Me
      Some Other Time
      Carried Away
      100 Easy Ways to Loose a Man
      Ohio
      The Wrong Note Rag
      Capital Gains
      If You Hadn't But You Did
      Catch Our Act at the Met
      On the Twentieth Century
      Our Private World
      I've Got It All
      The French Lesson
      Look Around
      Captain's Hook's Waltz
      Never Never Land
      Mysterious Lady
      Inspiration
    - Hal Prince Symposium, 2001 October 22; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616900)
    - Elaine Stritch Symposium, 2001 November 19; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616918)
    - 1600 Penn Ave
      - Act I, undated; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616926)
      - Opening, Act II, undated; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616934)
    - Performance by Dietz and Schwartz, 1989; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616942)
    - Begin [?] - 26 min, undated; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616959)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616967)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616975)
    - Keane master tape, 1983 November16; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616983)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104616991)
    - 1 + 2, undated; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104617007)
    - 3 + 4, 5 + 6, undated; 1 (Box 22, Item barcode 39002104617015)
- Oversize
  - Will Eisner note with illustration, undated (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Scrapbooks
    - Cabaret, 1966-1967 (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - Fiddler on the Roof, 1964-1966 (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Fiddler on the Roof, 1966-1967 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Flora, the Red Menace / The Ballad of the Sad Cafe, 1965 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum [stage production], 1962-1965 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum [film], 1965-1967 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Little Me, 1962-1965 (Box 29 (Oversize))